|     |
| --- |
| IP Engineering GmbH |

**Privacy Policy**

**Copyright**

The copyright for published content lies with IP Engineering GmbH or the mentioned owners. Any reproduction requires the prior written consent of the copyright holder.

**Disclaimer of liability**

IP Engineering GmbH carefully collects the information for these webpages and looks after their regular updating. Nevertheless, this data is to be understood as general information without guarantee that does not replace individual and profound consultation. IP Engineering GmbH accepts no liability for the topicality, correctness and completeness of the information on these pages or for trouble-free access at any time. IP Engineering GmbH does not assume any responsibility for the content of linked websites. As soon as you use such external links you leave the information offer of IP Engineering GmbH. Different rules may apply to the offers of third party, particularly with regard to data protection. Furthermore, IP Engineering GmbH excludes its liability for negligent breaches of duty with regard to services, in particular the downloading of files provided by IP Engineering GmbH on the Internet pages of IP Engineering GmbH In no case will IP Engineering be liable for any loss or damage of a material or immaterial nature arising from access to, use or non-use of published information, or from misuse of the connection or technical faults. All offers are not binding. IP Engineering reserves the right to change parts or the entire offer without prior notice, add to, delete or cease publication temporarily or permanently.

**Referrals and Links**

Linked websites are the responsibility of the respective operators. IP Engineering GmbH has no influence on the current and future content of the linked sites. Responsibility for information and services of linked sites rests entirely with the relevant third parties. No liability can be accepted in respect of the content of such websites.

**Data protection**

All personal data collected on the websites of IP Engineering GmbH are saved and processed only for your individual use, the transmission of information on products or the submission of service offers or to possibly be passed on to other companies of the owners of IP Engineering GmbH. IP Engineering GmbH assures you of treating your data confidentially and in accordance with the rules of the Federal Data Protection Act in effect.

**Handling of personal data**

Based of protection legislation, everyone has the right to the protection of their privacy, as well as to protection from misuse of their personal details. IP Engineering complies with these provisions. In cooperation with our hosting provider, we make every effort to protect the databases as good as possible from outside access, data loss, misuse or falsification. When accessing our websites only non-personal data such as your IP address, the last page visited, the browser used, date, time and general information about your operating systems respectively browser are transmitted anonymous to identify trends and improve our online services. Hence no conclusions are drawn on your person. Personal data will be treated in strict confidence and neither sold nor given to third parties.

**Cookies**

In certain cases, so-called Cookies are used. You can set your browser so that before saving a cookie, a warning appears on the screen. You can also dispense on the advantages of personal cookies. Certain services may not be used in this case.

**Social networks**

Some of the webpages may use plug-ins for the social networks Facebook, Google+, X (formerly Twitter), LinkedIn or YouTube. If you click on a social media plug-in, you will be redirected to the websites of the respective provider. Even if IP Engineering GmbH can be seen on these web pages, the data protection regulations of IP Engineering GmbH do not apply on these web pages, but the data protection regulations of the respective provider of the web page. If you have a user account with the respective provider, it is possible that the respective provider will add the information to your user account, for example, that you have switched from a website of IP Engineering to the website of the respective provider. The data protection regulations of the respective providers are to be taken from the websites of the respective providers or enquired from the respective providers. With most web browsers, if you can see in the address bar the domainname ip-engineering.com, then you are on IP Engineerings websites.

### About IP Engineering

IP Engineering GmbH is a company of consulting engineers, following tunnel ventilation and safety projects from the first ideas and concepts over feasibility studies, preliminary and detailed design, site supervision and operation - worldwide.

### Quick Links

### Follow us

© 2011-2024 IP Engineering GmbH, Aesch BL, Switzerland, Managing Director: Ludwig Ilg
